hello welcome to a slightly late
Saturday morning update I only do 20
minutes on Saturdays so that I can
attend the regularly scheduled at nine
o'clock Saturday morning project
roundtable for it together Tech in it
starts in half an hour at nine o'clock
so I'm on here for 20 nights to tell you
what I've done this week so I have been
live every game at 8:30 so I kept my
button seat and consistent so that is a
winning of itself
I think last Saturday is when I talked
about needing to get my marijuana in
some kind of control because I was doing
it all day every day and so I made the
goal of not doing it till noon and I did
in fact accomplish that which also was
part of instrumental me creating be
planting a garden I've been out weeding
and getting roots out of the out of the
soil which has been therapeutic really
fun to pull you my body's a little
complainy but yeah I'm gonna be in pain
and Mosel be in pain for the reason who
knows if it'll actually grow anything
but and this week I was gonna change it
to 2 p.m. but honestly I don't feel
ready to go up to 2 p.m. so I'm changing
it to 1 p.m. maybe for the first couple
weeks and then maybe I'll be able to
progress to two to two hours but hey
progress is progress I we had our first
live project raising this week on
Wednesday Kiera and Shiloh and Eric
joined me for a project raising on
mental health which was cool to have
that experience of doing it live we're
gonna do one this Wednesday the topic
both topics that were brought up are a
little confusing they're not quite like
transportation or education they're more
overarching one is kind of like how
they'll the systems intertwine and one's
the resiliency or rather of RIT like
redundancy and reserves and so figure
you know which one of those we're gonna
be talking about and getting people to
come chat about it will be a bit of a a
bit arduous well I'll figure it out
figure out what that is but we're gonna
do live budget regimes during this time
on Wednesdays I scheduled a meeting with
my regular communication partners that
we talk every week we're gonna talk
earlier on Wednesday than normal to
discuss the four questions and how to
use this time period to move forward so
I'm try not to make any decisions before
then because that is horrible mainly
that I know I'd be I'll have like five
epiphanies before them and everything
will change would be like we don't need
to have this conversation now figured it
out
but even that is as powerful of like
putting something off and then planning
it and then everything falls into place
is happen so many times oh I went have
this epiphany this week really yesterday
of how I've been I've been struggling
with coven 19 quarantine whatever we're
calling it as I'm sure everybody has but
I was struggling with my struggling
because I shouldn't be this is kind of
my life this is what I do all of the
almost all the time besides of course
not being able to my kid that can't go
to school and I can't go to cohousing
but other than that this is pretty
similar except that I haven't been going
out for my walks which are very
important I mean they're the only
exercise I really get plus they are just
like mentally I need them mentally
spiritually emotionally they're needed
and I can go out in them but it was like
I wasn't because I don't know there was
like this subconscious need to like
everyone's life was here before pandemic
and then everyone's kind of like got
miserable having to stay at home so it's
like I needed to equate that miss your
progress like everyone's life let's say
went down to 25% somehow I felt I needed
to go down at least like 75% which is
ridiculous because my life is actually
conducive to the quarantine pretty
pretty similar so I could keep my
lifestyle more or less so why aren't I
and part of it was again the
subconscious that everyone else staying
home had this impact on me because it
was simultaneously everyone's way more
productive at home that I am and
everyone's miserable at home when it's
actually in a lot of ways my highest
life
where a lot of my ideas have come from
it's where although force like kind of
like the pandemic I have found a lot of
beauty and purpose in it but the fact
that other people don't
isn't a reflection on mine and the fact
that other people were productive is in
a reflection online and the misery that
was coming from that was from me
comparing myself right other people are
more productive people are more
miserable than I have and so now that I
know that it's like right I don't need
to confirm myself to other people I
don't need to be baking bread I don't
need you to in Pinterest all I need to
do is follow the next right step and
it's okay if people are miserable this
isn't their thing this isn't all of
humanity probably doesn't have the same
course of action to stay at home and
hopefully I can offer some people
whoever find the message when I'm ready
to give it in is it's the same way that
they can find purpose in beauty at being
at home and I think a lot of people are
but it's all of it and I do feel all of
it I feel the isolation and the
difficulty of doing it and I also feel
the see the beauty and and I've got a
lot from my time having to be at home by
myself a lot of the time before before
this so that was just my realization and
in that so yesterday I was like okay I
went for a walk and I'm a single mom but
I live with my dad so I can like go out
and leave my kid running a grocery
shopping which I do all the time free Co
mid-nineteen because I don't want to
bring my kid grocery shopping does not
does not sound fun I think grocery shop
he didn't of itself but other than
leaving to do basically that one time
I've had and then with my kids in bed
and when she's in the other room I've
had no time to myself him to less monk I
don't think I really realized that and
so prioritizing going out and going for
a walk the place I normally go for a
walk his around this publicly owned Golf
Course and I because you are closing
you're passing other people on a trail I
was like is it gonna be closed I don't
know so I walked over there and in fact
they had
stitute because it's one big loop so
they had instituted a one-way policy
that you have to go one way and I was
like that's clea that make sense but
only runners and joggers can be on that
path and then they opened up the golf
course to everybody else so everyone
who's walking or just like you know your
kids on a bike or your kids on a scooter
they weren't really clear that bikes
weren't allowed so there was definitely
people on bikes in there and so I walked
around barefoot on a golf course
yesterday cuz it was exactly what I
needed and how often do you get to do
that I mean I love barefoot walking on
grass but generally you can't really do
it because it's hard grass and it's
anyway the Golf Course is perfect like
institute this always maybe have a day
of the week people come and do this but
it was just I don't know there was
because it was kid free time or like
outside outside of play my yard and my
immediate immediate neighborhood and so
there was just this like a little pocket
of magic that was pretty awesome but but
I saw anyway so I need to go for a walk
quite regularly during the week and the
fact that this is really nearby and it's
something that we'll all want to be open
during this time period it's gonna go
back to being a regular golf course and
there was like two people playing golf I
was like you realize this is not golf
right cuz it's a gun publicly owned so
because you can walk around in it
normally you pay the Greens fees you
play golf people like I could play free
golf no you can not will people are
walking around these do things do not go
in alignment together but like the
number and then realize seeing that when
I'm wearing a mat one I didn't need to
arm aspects when I was gonna be passing
people on me path I probably need to
wear mask but once I got there I'd like
took off my shoes I got five ask I was
like oh I get to like breathe and wander
freely there was somebody dancing and on
the big open green look like flying a
kite it looks so idealistic and I ideal
like there's a word there that I'm
missing but that's alright I'm gonna
keep this fairly short today I just want
to I'm gonna make sure I've updated on
everything their project raising stuff
so I have a conversation with the Omega
rule people to discuss the four
questions I have another conversation
scheduled for Monday on someone else's
world-changing project and I just put a
message out on my face personal Facebook
group because there's this local
pharming called abundance farm and
they're cooperatively owned or
cooperatively run it's a little
confusing because I'm not part of it but
the people who do the labor the people
who get the produce the people who are
so it's it's a community effort farm you
go out and anyway so I want to interview
the person who started it or runs it or
knows more about it and find out because
I think that that is a really good word
corporate structure sounds wrong for a
cooperative farm but the right corporate
structure and solution for right now in
in Florida and California there's a lot
of food that's rotting in the fields
because people of course are stuck
inside and although the usual method of
getting it out of the fields isn't
really in play right now are you getting
a lot of migrant workers on a bus out
there in camps to eat like that isn't
gonna work I have not changed my hair
color literally ever in my life I've
never dyed my hair but it does change
itself although that is that was one of
the things Thank You violet today
getting a haircut and when this thing
first started I've been watching these
YouTube videos oh I don't know some guy
who looks at he has like millions of
subscribers he's some peopie he's like
blonde he's just like a really sweet
nice I was expecting kind of caddy and
he's just like really sweet and nice
about people's hair he's a hairdresser
he watches people do their there and ya
know my hair's Auburn it's always a my
hair color but it like switches
throughout the year between like and
depending on the sunlight depending on
the respite it's not it's not dyed
anyway so I'm when this everyone was
first quarantined I was gonna go and get
a haircut right before I went to
Edmonton and I didn't and so then I was
gonna get a haircut it had been two in
which of course we didn't leave the
apartment so that was not an option and
when I got back hairdressers were done
and so I reached out to my hairdresser
and was like you know what you should do
is you should do like a pretty much
YouTube view tutorials like you should
have your clients walk them through it
and I'm just entertaining right it's
kind of like Pinterest fails for her
hair her walking through hair cut is not
the same as going into one like a
professional and I love my hairdresser
we're friends and anyway so so she was
like no that would give me too much
anxiety I'm not gonna do that but then
he yesterday she posted on her facebook
anyone want to do is zoom Erica I'll
walk you through anyone with a short
haircut want to do Clippers and my dad
has Clippers because he's got really
short hair so we're gonna try it today
I'm gonna ask her we're gonna do it on
soo but if it's just the two of us I'm
gonna ask to record it and I might post
it on this post on the YouTube channel
should I say sir all that meandering
through life because honestly however it
ends up I mean I don't want no hair I
don't think I'll shave my hair
completely because part of my um
stamina's doing that so I'm a hair cut I
love it because it works out oh yeah I'm
good with everything has security issues
literally everything so I just assume
anything online is watched by like
Zuckerberg Bill Gates and like nefarious
characters like people who know the name
of we're trying to steal my identity and
stuff I don't think Zuckerberg steal my
identity he's fully openly see whatever
dominates identity everyone's data
information um yeah I had security
issues again I'm not doing anything in
there that I'm willing to do basically
everything live on YouTube itself so
having Zumbi again I just assume
everything online have security issues
until we own it together and we can see
what is in place for security and feels
right with it it's basically everything
you put out there was was you know I've
seen a bunch of things like my kids
school won't allow them to go on zoom'
they can't do it on zoom and so instead
they're using Microsoft teams and I
don't like it whatever and so I'm gonna
so I have this I'm gonna get off right
away because I don't stay on for an hour
today because I have the regular
Saturday morning scheduled thing that we
do at 9:00 o'clock
very protective of your pet rock
collection like you don't want it online
then people might come and take rocks I
somewhat what's the word protective like
having my kid on screen she has her own
YouTube channel and like our one I'm
like don't use your name the don't I've
used her name several times though and
then she like hub and just pop on camera
with me I'm like stop well if you ever
want to share your pet rocks on camera
on YouTube make them unfamous cuz
there's no paper one or two people
watching but anyway so today I'm assume
say her welcome to come on and show them
that rocks are not something my kid I
the thing she gets attached to and love
cuz she had this stick
she called Twiggy we were horseback
riding for like a week with her school
last year which was amazing but we
almost like she lost it so many times
that on this horse ranch for every or
the horses are running around wild
basically until night any other ones
that aren't being out ridden and she lot
like left to stick somewhere she wanted
me to find she found it like three or
four times a word to men to leave she
was distraught who couldn't find an end
up be in the bathroom we brought it home
the rocks couldn't said fair enough fair
enough I don't know how to convene with
rocks but if you know how to convene the
frogs go ahead ask I'm having so this I
want to be continuing next week but this
not smoking pot until 1 p.m.
next week which seems like enough of a
little bit of an incremental change and
then have Saturday morning session which
I'm really excited because that's also
something that although I don't think
I've had any direct that's the word
impact on it together tech stuff seems
to be taking off more so yesterday for
our Friday idea cafe we had five of us
instead of just the regular three of us
which was great and I think this morning
we're also gonna have AP people more
people at the roundtable to discuss our
projects and so that feels good because
like it's been a lot of trying different
things and it's just a nature Levin who
show up constantly and try like what
would make this better but it's partly
Facebook's algorithm so I'm excited for
that this week like I said on we're
gonna do a solution or a zine on
Wednesday I'm reaching out to people
from abundance farm because one of the
things I want to do with this time
period
is interview different people or have a
conversation really with different
people on camera who are doing different
various projects offer real hope right
now in the in the realm of of health
care and food scarcity and just
community and connection and technology
and I feel like I have enough people in
my sphere and directly related to my
sphere like friends acquaintances and
friends of friends to reach out like I
again abundance far Remzi with common
planet and Nicole with the transition if
they're willing to unavailable 8:30 I
will happily schedule a conversation
with them and introduce you to their
amazing projects all of which are in my
mind I'm changing so that is partly what
I'm gonna do and that I'm holding off on
making too much plans for these hour
sessions because of one yesterday's
coaching session that I got that it's
just supposed to unfold naturally that's
also it we did yesterday we did live
cook life coaching live online but
nobody showed nobody showed up to want
it so I did it on myself that makes
sense so hopefully next time we do that
there's somebody else to participate but
I enjoyed the process and if other
people want to be coached and find out
what their subconscious is offering them
for solutions that will be great
otherwise I am allowing me this process
all the way to unfold because these four
questions I don't even know and you're
not to get into them we both have one
day a week that it's just about the four
questions which is what I would love I
would love someone to come on and we can
explore the four questions with them and
explore them together and create a world
that works for everyone I'm gonna get
off before 20 minutes I time is
something that I know we have stay on 20
minutes I said 20 minutes I'm done I'm
done with the update that's these ones
are short every other day I post the
link on YouTube and I try to go on to
Twitter and post it there as well so
that people can join me on camera if
they would like but during the Saturday
mornings it's only 20 minutes so don't
do that so I will see you tomorrow at
8:30 I don't know what we're doing yet
we will see and if you want to watch me
in your good ten minutes over on
together
channel is in the description in on
YouTube - police save the world by
beyond rating three life I need to
acronym it's like but after they all
have several Friday's that's okay and
this my I can't acronym it I couldn't
remember the order of acronyms so if you
want to catch us there at the
descriptions in the the link is in the
description for the together tech
channel I'm gonna be there with Adrian
Bentley and whoever else shows up to
talk about our individual projects my
project right now is solution raising
focusing on how to what could we create
together if we had 10,000 people
$100,000 in various sectors of society
what kind of voluntary amazing solutions
could we co-create together and then
figuring out a process to actually
create them and a trails project is wiki
election that lays this recent score and
we yesterday we had someone who has a
who has a food sovereignty project and
then somebody who has a reconciliation
understanding the treaties of North
America turtle island and it's amazing
it's amazing to have different different
people in here with what they're up to
in the world so I will be going to do
that and let me said it starts a
ten-minute so I gotta go take care
[Music]